http://www.daviesharley.com/privacy-policy

PRIVACY POLICY
INTRODUCTIONThe purpose of this statement is to show our strong commitment in ensuring user privacy. We understand that often users are concerned about the use and storage of personal information, and the security we offer in regards to such information. Protecting the privacy and the confidentiality of personal information of users/customers over the Internet, on the telephone, or through our offices has always been fundamental to the way E-Dealer conducts its affairs.POLICY STATEMENTThis policy deals only with personal information handled by the websites owned by E-Dealer. Personal information relates to any information about an identifiable individual, excluding business contact information. The following content depicts how E-Dealer handles personal information. E-Dealer has the right at any time to change, alter, add and/or remove portions of the Terms of Use by updating the contents of this page. You are advised to periodically visit this page and review current Terms of Use. E-Dealer, at its sole discretion, and without prior notice reserves the right to alter or discontinue any aspect or feature of this Website, including but not limited to, the content, equipment and software needed for access or use, and minimum equipment and software requirements of this Website.ACCOUNTABILITYTHIS WEB SITE AND THE INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS AND SERVICES ASSOCIATED WITH IT ARE PROVIDED "AS IS." E-DEALER, AND/OR PARTICIPATING LENDERS, TO THE FULLEST EXTENT ON THE LAW, DISCLAIM ANY WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, AS TO ANY MATTER WHATSOEVER RELATING TO THIS WEB SITE AND ANY INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS AND SERVICES PROVIDED HEREIN, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE, AND NONINFRINGEMENT OF THIRD PARTY RIGHTS. USE OF THIS WEB SITE AND/OR E-DEALER SERVICES IS AT YOUR OWN RISK. E-DEALER AND/OR PARTICIPATING LENDERS ARE NOT LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OR OTHER INJURY ARISING OUT OF OR IN ANY WAY CONNECTED WITH THE USE OF THIS WEB SITE AND/OR E-DEALER’S SERVICES OR WITH THE DELAY OR INABILITY TO USE THIS WEB SITE, OR FOR ANY INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS AND SERVICES OBTAINED THROUGH THIS WEB SITE, OR OTHERWISE ARISING OUT OF THE USE OF THIS WEB SITE, WHETHER RESULTING IN WHOLE OR IN PART, FROM BREACH OF CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE, STRICT LIABILITY OR OTHERWISE, EVEN IF E-DEALER AND/OR ITS SUPPLIERS HAD BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF DAMAGES. E-DEALER ARE ALSO TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, IN NO EVENT SHALL WE BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES OF ANY KIND ARISING FROM YOUR USE OF A SITE OR FOR THE UNAUTHORIZED MODIFICATION OF TEXT OR ADVERTISEMENTS PROVIDED BY US TO OUR MARKETING PARTNERS OR THIRD PARTIES.This Web site may contain links to web sites maintained by third parties, or advertising for a third party. Such links or advertising are provided and/or created by the owners of the website and E-Dealer does not operate or control in any respect any information, software, products or services available on such Websites. The inclusion of a link to a web site, apart from that of E-Dealer, is done so at the discretion of the owner and does not imply any endorsement of the services or the site, its contents, or its sponsoring organization. E-Dealer is not responsible for any errors or delays in responding to a qualification form or referral form caused by an incorrect e-mail address or other such personal information required provided by you or other technical problems beyond our reasonable control. This Website contains information for and is designed for use in Canada and for that requiring Canadian vehicle information. If you access this Website outside of Canada, you will hold E-Dealer harmless in the event that accessing information on the Website is in violation of your local laws. Exporting information from the Website is subject to all export laws and you will hold E-Dealer harmless should any export of information from the Website be considered as a violation to local laws.COLLECTION AND RELEASE OF INFORMATIONThe purpose for which personal information is collected will be identified at or before the time the information is collected. Personal information may be collected for the following purposes:Request for a vehicle service appointment, general appointment or for the purpose of booking a test driveRequest for a quotation of a vehicle, a part/parts or accessories or ask a technicianRequest general information to be sent regarding a vehicle or for contacting the dealerRegister for a trade-in of a vehicle or buying a carRegistering in for feedback or comments or sharing/emailing information to a friendRegistering and/or submitting credit application - users allow us and our affiliates to make personally identifiable information available to third parties in accordance with the terms of this privacy policyE-Dealer uses information gathered about users only for limited purposes permitted by law. Information collected is needed for and directly corresponds to processing loan applications, administering loan accounts, providing services to customers, providing customers and website visitors with information about site services, and to fulfill any legal and regulatory requirements. Information is retained by and is not otherwise transferred outside the confines of E-Dealer and its clients, unless permission to do so has been requested or as permitted by law. While on this site we may collect “Personal Information” from you. We may collect or expand to collect, the internet service providers of visitors. This information is used to improve the performance of the site and the credit application, enhance the user experience and ensure the satisfaction of site visitors, as well as to assist with systems administration, and to resolve problems. The information tracked may or may expand to include, but is not exclusive to, the type of operating system in use, the type of browser used by the visitor, the pages visited and data requested. We use this information internally to analyze site traffic. From time to time we may create or conduct analyses and summary reports about the operation of the website. For your comfort and ease of accessibility we collect website data viewed. This is done in order to recommend the right kind of options to you specifically ones you would be interested in.IP ADDRESSESAn IP address is a number automatically assigned to your computer whenever you access the Internet. All computer identification on the Internet is conducted with IP addresses, which allow computers and servers to recognize and communicate with each other. Your IP address may be used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information about you, to conduct site analysis. E-Dealer may collect or expand to collect IP addresses in order to conduct system administration, diagnose problems and to better serve you in using the services and features within the site, namely the credit application.SECURITYE-Dealer has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under site control. Any employee or contractor requiring access to user information must be approved and must use information of the uses outlined in this document. Access is reviewed on a regular basis. E-Dealer also uses extensive and sophisticated secure technology to protect your data and transmissions between you and banks, lenders and loan brokers participating in E-Dealer products and services. Transmission between browsers and our web server, as well as participating lenders is implemented using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. Given that no technology is foolproof, we must also advise users that there will always remain a certain amount of risk and that your personal information may be disclosed, without your consent, unintentionally, and without fault on the part of E-Dealer. We decline any responsibility in the event that such confidential information is disclosed.ANTI-SPAM POLICYOur Anti-Spam Policy tolerates only permission-based email – subscription to emails or information requested for to be provided through email or phone. You may choose to opt-out of our mailing list. By checking the opt-in box when contacting us - through the forms available - you agree to be contacted by us for the purposes described in the Disclaimer. All emails sent to you will be compliant with CASL and will include:The option to opt-in to receive communication for the purposes described in DisclaimerThe option to unsubscribe from receiving electronic communication from us as described hereAt any point in time you may opt out from receiving communication from us by - clicking the link at the bottom of our communications which indicates “unsubscribe” or call us to indicate not to receive calls for promotional purposes.USER INFORMATION FOR THOSE UNDER 18You must be at least 18 years old to have our permission to use our credit application. To protect the interests of children, no information should be submitted to our web sites by children 18 years of age or under, without the consent of a parent or guardian. E-Dealer cannot be held liable for information unknowingly given to us by any under-age user, but does not actively seek any demographic or preference information from children, nor will it ever knowingly disclose any personally identifying information regarding children to third parties.INDEMNITYAs a condition of use of this web site, credit application and/or E-Dealer's services, you agree to indemnify E-Dealer and its suppliers, participating Lenders, or real estate professionals from and against any and all liabilities, expenses (including attorneys' fees) and damages arising out of claims resulting from your use of this web site and credit application, including without limitation of any claims alleging facts that if true would constitute a breach by you of this Agreement.PaymentUnfortunately, we do not take personal cheques. Deposits must be made with cash, credit card or money order.
